ddc-web.com 2002-12-02

# Data Device Corporation: Privacy Profile

Business Policies   
Privacy Policy

### Introduction

Data Device Corporation is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected and that we comply with your rights resulting from the European Data Protection Directive (“the Directive”).  This policy explains how we use the personal information we collect about you and the procedures that we have in place to safeguard your privacy and your rights resulting from the Directive.

### How we collect your information 

We may retain any personal information that is received from you.  For example, this might include your name and brief details of a query or an order made by you.  However, we do not normally retain order details.  We may also retain personal information relating to you that is in the public domain.  For example, personal details which are published on a web site operated by you or in a telephone directory.

### How we use your information

We will retain and use any personal information received from you in connection with the provision of our services, marketing, administration and the keeping of accounts and records relating to our business.  In particular, we retain personal information received from you in order to establish and develop an order history.  The order history records brief details of the queries and orders made by you. 

We consider that the personal information that we hold about you is adequate, relevant and not excessive in order to enable us to provide services to you, undertake marketing activities and to administer and keep accounts and records relating to our business.

As part of our customer communication program, the personal information about you that is held by us will be accessible via our customer database by certain authorised employees at our corporate headquarters and at our regional sales office in the region in which you are situated.  This is in order that we can provide you with fast and efficient customer services, sales and technical support, from whichever office you contact.

Subject to the preceding paragraph, we shall not transfer or otherwise disclose to any third party any personal information about you, unless we have your explicit consent to such transfer or disclosure or unless such transfer or disclosure is required by law or other court order.

From time to time, we may contact you to invite you to tradeshows where our products will be displayed.  If you do not wish to receive such invitations, please notify:

Karen Robinson, Director of Marketing Communications  
Data Device Corporation  
Telephone:  (631l) 567-5600  
e-mail:  robinson@ddc-web.com

### Updating your information

We try to ensure that the personal details that we hold about you are accurate.  In order to help us achieve this objective, if any of the personal information that you have provided to us changes, please notify:

Jill Thatcher  
DDC U.K. LTD.  
Fax:  9-011-44-1635-32264  
Phone:  9-011-44-1635-811140  
or the person with whom you are used to dealing. 

### How we protect your information

We take security issues very seriously and abide by strict internal standards.  We take all reasonable steps to keep your information confidential.  Our internal procedures cover the storage, access and disclosure of your information.

We have an information security policy, which sets out management commitment to information security within our organisation and provides clear direction on responsibilities and procedures.  This policy lists the measures to be taken for the purpose of protecting against unauthorised or unlawful processing of your personal information.

We have trained our employees in security systems and procedures and on the importance of keeping your information confidential. 

Access to all of our offices, sites, buildings, computer rooms, desks, storage areas, equipment, and other facilities is restricted to authorised persons.  We also place controls on access to certain information.  Such controls include monitoring and logging access so as to assist in detecting and investigating security breaches or attempted breaches when they occur. 

We are currently developing a business continuity plan, which is a contingency plan which identifies the business functions and assets (including personal data) which would need to be maintained in the event of a disaster and sets out the procedures for protecting them and restoring them if necessary.

### Making your information available to countries outside the EEA

Because of the international nature of our business, our customer database is accessible by certain authorised employees at our corporate headquarters and at our regional sales office in the region in which you are situated .  For your information, the addresses of our corporate headquarters and each of our regional sales offices are set out in the Schedule to this privacy policy.

Accordingly, we confirm that:

1.                   we will disclose your personal information to certain authorised employees at our corporate headquarters and at our regional sales office in the region in which you are situated;

(this might be by entering your personal details into our customer database or by transferring such details in person, over the telephone, by post, by facsimile or by email);

2.                   certain authorised employees at our corporate headquarters and at our regional sales office in the region in which you are situated will process and hold your personal information; and

3.                   in doing so, we may be transferring your personal information from a country within the European Economic Area (“EEA”) to a country outside the EEA that may not have the same level of data protection as countries within the EEA.

However, as we are committed to protecting your personal information, each of our corporate headquarters and our regional sales offices confirm that they will:

(a)                 not use or disclose your personal information except as set out in this privacy policy; and

(b)                 take appropriate technical and organisational security measures against the unauthorised or unlawful processing of your personal information and against the accidental loss or destruction of, or damage to, your personal information.

### General

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time.  If we change our privacy policy we will send you the revised privacy policy, so that you may be aware of the information we collect and how we use it. 

This privacy policy is not intended to, and does not, create any contractual or other legal rights.  This privacy policy does not affect any of your rights resulting from the Directive.

We welcome your views about our privacy policy.  If you would like to contact us with any queries or comments please contact:

Martha Solowey  
Data Device Corporation  
105 Wilbur Place, Bohemia, New York 11716  
USA  
Telephone:  (631) 567-5600  
Fax:  (631) 563-5204  
e-mail:  Solowey@ddc-web.com  
or the person with whom you are used to dealing.

### Your consent

By providing your personal information to us, you consent to the use of your personal information as set out in this privacy policy. 

#### Corporate Headquarters

Data Device Corporation  
105 Wilbur Place  
Bohemia  
NY 11716  
USA  

#### Regional Sales Offices  
  
---  
**Southeast, U.S.A**  
21400 Ridgetop Circle  
Suite 110  
Sterling  
VA 20166  
USA | **West Coast, U.S.A.**  
5912 Bolsa Ave.  
Suite 201  
Huntington Beach  
CA 92649  
USA  
**United Kingdom**  
DDC (United Kingdom) Limited  
9-14 Cheap Street  
Newbury, Berkshire  
RG14 5DD  
UK | **Germany**  
DDC Elektronik GmbH  
Ahornstrasse 2  
82296 Schoengeising  
Germany  
**France**  
DDC Electronique  
10 Rue Carle-Herbert  
92400 Courbevoie  
France | **Japan**  
DDC Electronics K.K.  
Koraku 1-Chome Bldg. 7F  
2-8 Koraku  
Tokyo 112  
Japan  
  
#### Click here to download a PDF version of our Privacy Policy
